gagatrends.com 2013-06-09

# 

GaGa Trends Online must keep and use customer data reliably. We value your trust and will never sell your information to third parties.

### Customer personal information and how it’s used?

Personal information is considered any information that is definite to you, such as your email address, credit card information, name, body measurement etc.

When you make a purchase, we need your address, phone number and credit card information (if purchasing by credit card). This information is amassed in a secure database, only open to selected employees with access rights to this information. 

Additionally, The GaGa Trends Online logs your Internet Protocol Address (IP). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when browsing the Internet. Information from IP addresses is used for system administration, to examine overall traffic trends, troubleshooting, etc. This information is used only in the aggregate form. IP addresses are not linked to any PII, meaning that your session on our site is tracked, but will not be linked to any personal information.

### How protected is my personal information?

Customer information is protected with GaGa Trends Online! To protect customer order information is a main concern. Only selected and related employees can access the customer data with the permission of the company owner. So customer payment details, measurement details, email addresses and home or office addresses are very secure.

### Get in touch with

You can speak to us via e-mail at [ info@gagatrendsonline.co.uk](mailto:info@thetrendystyle.com) and you can also contact us via telephonic, postal address reveal on GaGa Trends Online “Contact Us” page.

### Updates to this policy

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be alert of what information we collect, utilize and reveal. We push you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@gagaatrendsonline.co.uk](mailto:info@thetrendystyle.com)
